actionbux.com 2015-03-15

# ActionBux | Privacy Policy

_Last update: November 26th 2014_

ActionBux is committed to respecting the privacy concerns of its visitors to ActionBux.com (“the Website”). Company has created this Privacy Policy (the “Policy”) to establish guidelines that will govern the collection, use, protection and disclosure of the personal and non-personal information of its visitors.

N.E.K Advanced Solutions Inc. is the parent company of ActionBux.com; any reference to ActionBux.com is by incorporation a reference to N.E.K. Advanced Solutions Inc.

The User shall agree to all terms and conditions set forth in this Policy. The Company may, at any time, choose to edit, add and/or delete portions of this agreement and impose changes without prior notification of its members or Users.

**I. Information Collecting**

ActionBux collect information from the User when a User registers on ActionBux. Registration requires a User submitting all required personal and business information.

When ordering or registering on ActionBux, Users may be asked to enter his or her: name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number, and date of birth or other personal identification information as may be necessary. Users may, however, visit the Website anonymously.

**II. Use of User Information**

Any of the information ActionBux collect from the User may be used in one of the following ways;

(a) To personalize the User’s experience. User information helps ActionBux to better respond to your individual needs;

(b) To improve the Website’s performance;

(c) To improve customer service;

(d) To swiftly, legally and accurately process transactions. User information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without the User’s consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested;

(e) To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature;

(f) To send periodic emails or other communications to the User; and

(g) Any other manner that is consistent with the User Agreement and Privacy Policy.

**III. Use of Cookies**

ActionBux uses Cookies (small files placed on the User’s hard drive through a Web browser – if allowed by the User – that enables ActionBux to recognize the User’s browser and capture and remember certain information).

ActionBux shall use Cookies according to the following;

(a) To help identify you and maintain your signed-in status;

(b) Cookies are ‘session cookies’, meaning that they are automatically deleted from the User’s hard drive at the end of a session;

(c) Users may decline ActionBux’s cookies if the User’s browser permits, although doing so may interfere with the User’s accessibility to the Website or services;

(d) Users may encounter cookies from third parties on certain pages of the sites that ActionBux do not control; and

(e) Any other manner that is consistent with the User Agreement and Privacy Policy.

**IV. Third-Party Interactions**

ActionBux shall not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties User’s personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist ActionBux in operating the Website, conducting business, or servicing the User. Third Parties agree to keep all User information confidential.

ActionBux may also release User information when release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

**V. California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**

ActionBux have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. ActionBux therefore will not distribute User’s personal information to outside parties without your consent. As part of the California Online Privacy Protection Act, all Users of our site may make any changes to their information at any time by logging into their accounts and going to the ‘Profile and Settings’ page.

**VI. Application of Privacy Policy**

The Policy applies only to information collected through ActionBux website and not to information collected offline.

**VII. User Consent**

By using the ActionBux website the User consents to this Policy in its entirety. There is no severability.

This Policy is subject to periodic change and alterations. AuctionBux will post the latest update date on the top of the homepage, by continuing to use AuctionBux, a User shall give their implied acceptance to the new terms of this Agreement.

ActionBux’s failure to enforce the Policy’s strict performance of any provision of this Policy will not constitute a waiver of our right to subsequently enforce such provision or any other provision of this Policy.

THIS IS A LEGAL AGREEMENT BETWEEN YOU AND ActionBux AND BY REGISTERING THE USER AGREES TO BE BOUND BY THE TERMS AND CONDITIONS OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY. BY ACCEPTING THIS PRIVACY POLICY YOU ARE HEREBY BOUND TO THE RULES AND GUIDELINES LISTED ABOVE. PLEASE READ THIS ENTIRE USER AGREEMENT CAREFULLY BEFORE ACCEPTING ITS TERMS.
